[
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950161",
      "correctAnswer": "J.R.R. Tolkien",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Roald Dahl",
        "George R.R. Martin",
        "Brandon Sanderson"
      ],
      "question": "Who wrote \"The Hobbit\"?",
      "tags": [
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951364",
      "correctAnswer": "Mural",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Sculpture",
        "Graffiti",
        "Mozaic"
      ],
      "question": "A large painting or decoration done on a wall is known as what?",
      "tags": [
        "art",
        "words",
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9501a9",
      "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Voyages Extraordinaires",
        "Percy Jackson & the Olympians",
        "Twilight"
      ],
      "question": "In which book series does 'Neville Longbottom' appear?",
      "tags": [
        "fictitious_characters",
        "literature",
        "young_adult",
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95139b",
      "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Voyages Extraordinaires",
        "Percy Jackson & the Olympians",
        "Twilight"
      ],
      "question": "In which book series does 'Ginny Weasley' appear?",
      "tags": [
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950ebe",
      "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Christopher Tolkien",
        "Philip Pullman",
        "C. S. Lewis"
      ],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'Harry Potter'?",
      "tags": [
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950eb2",
      "correctAnswer": "Charles Darwin",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Percy Bysshe Shelley",
        "H. Rider Haggard",
        "Robert Louis Stevenson"
      ],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'The Origin of Species'?",
      "tags": [
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950eeb",
      "correctAnswer": "Charles Dickens",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Oscar Wilde",
        "Joseph Conrad",
        "Henryk Sienkiewicz"
      ],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'Great Expectations'?",
      "tags": [
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95139d",
      "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Percy Jackson & the Olympians",
        "The Hunger Games",
        "His Dark Materials"
      ],
      "question": "In which book series does 'Hagrid' appear?",
      "tags": [
        "fictitious_characters",
        "literature",
        "young_adult",
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950e77",
      "correctAnswer": "C. S. Lewis",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Neil Gaiman",
        "Jack Vance",
        "Douglas Adams"
      ],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'The Chronicles of Narnia'?",
      "tags": [
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c3b7cc59eab6f9513d1",
      "correctAnswer": "The Chronicles of Narnia",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Percy Jackson & the Olympians",
        "Divergent",
        "The Hunger Games"
      ],
      "question": "In which book series would you find the character of 'Aslan'?",
      "tags": [
        "literature",
        "fictitious_characters",
        "young_adult",
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95136a",
      "correctAnswer": "Collage",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Watercolor",
        "Sculpture",
        "Pointilism"
      ],
      "question": "What is the word for a composition made of cut and pasted pieces of materials?",
      "tags": [
        "art",
        "words",
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950f48",
      "correctAnswer": "J. R. R. Tolkien",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "G. K. Chesterton",
        "Philip Pullman",
        "C. S. Lewis"
      ],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'The Hobbit'?",
      "tags": [
        "fantasy",
        "literature",
        "people",
        "general_knowledge",
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f95139e",
      "correctAnswer": "Harry Potter",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Voyages Extraordinaires",
        "Percy Jackson & the Olympians",
        "Twilight"
      ],
      "question": "In which book series does 'Severus Snape' appear?",
      "tags": [
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950eae",
      "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Christopher Tolkien",
        "Philip Pullman",
        "C. S. Lewis"
      ],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire'?",
      "tags": [
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    },
    {
      "category": "Arts & Literature",
      "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950eb1",
      "correctAnswer": "J. K. Rowling",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Christopher Tolkien",
        "Philip Pullman",
        "C. S. Lewis"
      ],
      "question": "Which author wrote 'Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets'?",
      "tags": [
        "harry_potter",
        "literature",
        "general_knowledge",
        "arts_and_literature"
      ],
      "type": "Multiple Choice",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "regions": []
    }
  ]